nice to meet you.
初めまして
Are you nervous?
緊 張してますか?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
I agree.
そうですね
There's a good-looking guy nearby.
近くにイケメンですもんね
Are you handsome?
イケメンなんですか?
What type of system is it?
どういう系がタイプですか?
It's Tsuda Masaki type.
つだまさき系です
Do you think old clothes look good on you?
古着が似合う感じの?
that's right.
そうです
It's definitely the rags I wore.
確かに僕着たボロ着ですね
I see.
なるほど
So I guess I like that kind of refreshing skin.
じゃあちょっとああいう爽やかな感じの 肌が好きなんですね
I think you're a little nervous,
ちょっとさ、緊張してると思うからさ、
I'm going to ask you a lot of questions.
いろいろ質問をしていくからさ
Please answer without being able to answer.
答えられないで答えてください
Do you have a boyfriend now?
彼氏とか今いるの?
I have a boyfriend.
彼氏います
yes.
はい
Is that Tsuda Masaki type?
それはつだまさき系ですか?
It's Tsuda Masaki type.
つだまさき系です
Have you been together for quite some time?
結構付き合って長いですか?
About half a year.
半年くらいです
Which one would you like first?
最初はどっちかお?
contents?
中身?
First is the face.
最初は顔ですね
It was cool.
かっこよかったんだ
I'm jealous.
羨ましいですね
It's beautiful.
綺麗なね
I hope you can get along with your shoulders.
肩とね、付き合えてね
So, where do you go on dates?
で、どういうとこデート行っているの?
My hometown is Kyoto, so anything is possible.
地元が京都なんで、 何でもあるんで
That's right.
そうなんだ
It's not as prosperous as Tokyo, though.
東京よりは栄えてないですけど
But on the other hand, if you go all the way,
でも逆にね、 ず っと行ったらね、
That's right.
そうですよね
I don't really eat Japanese food.
日本食とかあんま食わないですよね、
perhaps.
たぶん
I sometimes eat Japanese food.
日本食たまに食べますね
Are you going to eat it?
食べるんですか?
Sometimes though.
たまにですけど
It's a stylish date.
おしゃれなデートですね
I see.
なるほど
Quite indoors and outdoors.
結構インドア、アウトドア
I'm an indoor person.
インドアの方です
I see.
なるほど
Do you have any hobbies?
趣味とかあったりするの?
I like games.
ゲームが好きです
ゲーム好きなんだ
What game?
何ゲーム?
Combat battle system.
戦闘バトル系
Like CALL OF BEAUTY?
CALL OF BEAUTYみたいな?
That's what it feels like.
そういう感じです
That's surprising.
意外ですね
I thought that kind of thing would be a little scary.
そういうのちょっと怖いみたいな感じかと思ったら
Are you going hard?
ガンガンいけちゃいます?
Yes, I can go.
はい、いけちゃいます
That's a good gap.
いいギャップですね
Well, I like middle-class ones.
結構じゃあ、中系のやつが好きなんだ
I agree.
そうですね
Do you understand ground safety?
グ ラ ンド セーフとか分かります?
There is a record.
記録があります
Is it okay if I ask you your age now?
今、年齢とかって聞いても平気?
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳です
You're young.
若いですね
Your skin is beautiful.
肌とか綺麗ですもんね
I'm only 20 years old.
まだ20歳なんで
What about care?
ケアとかは?
I'm doing it right.
ちゃんとしてますよ
What are you doing?
何してるんですか?
I haven't done anything special, but
そんな特別なことしてないですけど、
I'm very particular about lotions and serums.
化粧水とか美容液はちゃんとこだわってて
Is that how you feel?
そういう感じですか?
It looks like a parasol.
日 傘似合いそうですね
It stings a lot in the summer.
夏はよく刺しますね
It really suits you.
なんかすごい似合ってますね
I don't think it's the other way around.
逆になってないと思う
In places like Kyoto, it doesn't feel like a parasol.
京都とかでは日傘って感じじゃないもんね
It feels like it's stabbing me.
さって刺すみたいな感じなんだね
I see.
なるほど ね
Are you a student now?
今って学生さん?
Or are you doing something?
それとも何かやってるの?
I'm a student.
学生です
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
I see.
なるほど
By the way, can I tell you which university?
ちなみにどこの大学とかって教えてもいいですか?
I guess it's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいかな
To be seen?
見ばれ的に?
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
I'm going to clean it up a little bit, if you don't mind.
ちょっと手入れるんで、もしよかったらちょっと
Then please keep it a secret.
じゃあ内緒にしてくださいね
Kyoto Women's University.
京都女子大学です
I feel like a girl in a box.
箱入り娘って感じですね
is that so?
そうですか?
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
Are the academic subjects too strict?
学科まで厳しいですか?
Can you put me in subjects A and P?
学 科A、P入れてくれますか?
I'll put it in. Of course.
入れます入れますもちろん
Absolutely.
絶対ですよ
Department of Contemporary Sociology.
現代社会学科です
So you like history?
じゃあ歴史好きなんですね
I agree.
そうですね
I really like history.
結構歴史好きです
It feels really solid and solid.
本当に固て固てな感じですね
But it's not a Japanese sword.
でも日本刀じゃないんだね
My hobbies are.
趣味はね
It's free, isn't it?
自由なんだね
It's cute.
かわいいですね
Well, I'm from Kyoto, so...
そしたらね、ちょっとね、京都の方なんで、
I thought I'd like to ask you some questions,
ちょっと僕もいろいろ ご質問したいなと思って、
I have a question about Kyoto.
京都について質問するんですけど、
Do you like Edge?
エッジとかは好きですか?
Well, do you like it?
えー、好きですかね
Oh, don't you hate it?
あ、嫌いではない?
When was the last time?
最近いつしました?
Recently about 3 days ago.
最近3日前くらい
Ah, it's quite recent.
あ、結構最近ですね
It was the day I met my boyfriend's parents.
ちょうど彼親と会った日だったんで
That's just a simple thing to do.
ほやほやってことですね
Do you masturbate?
オナニーとかしたりするの?
No, not at all.
いや、全くしないです
What do you do when you're horny?
ムラムラした時とかどうしてるの?
Not really.
ないですよね
There aren't that many.
あんまないんだ
That's true if you're with your boyfriend.
彼氏といたらそれはありますけど
Yes, yes, yes.
はい はいはい
Don't you get lonely often?
寂しくなったりもあんまない?
It's more fun to play with friends.
それより友達とか遊んでる方が楽しいんだ
I see.
なるほどね
I'm fine as long as I can answer, but
答えられる範囲で大丈夫なんだけど、
Just in case, he told me about it at the press store today,
一応ね、今日、 記者店では話してくれたけど、
I'm here. Is it okay if I ask about Burdock's motive?
来たね、 ごぼう動機とかって 聞いても平気かな?
I came here because I wanted to live alone and needed the funds to do so.
一人暮らしがしたくって、 その 資金が欲しくて来ました
Like moving?
引っ越し的な?
Yes, like moving.
はい、引っ越し的な
I need some money.
ちょっとまとまったお金が必要なんだ
Are you currently working part-time?
バイトとか今してるの?
No, I can't do it because my parents are strict.
いや、親が厳しくってできないんですよ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんですね
Yes, yes, yes.
はいはいはい
By the way, what do your parents do?
ちなみに親は何やってる方なんですか?
Oh, I run a clothing store.
あ、ご服屋さんやってます
I see.
なるほどね
He said he would be a little hurt by that one in my house.
ちょっと うちのあれに傷つくだろうっていう
I agree.
そうですね
Do you feel like it will continue in the future?
将来は続く感じなのかな?
In the future, I'll still be a university student, so I guess I'll just focus on my studies.
将来、まだ大学生なんで、 とりあえず学業に励んでっていう感じ
That's right.
ですね
It's good to be encouraged.
励 むっていいですね
That's a fancy way of saying it.
おしゃれな言い方ですね
Well then, let's talk about the subject from earlier.
したらね、 じゃあ ね、さっきの学科ではさ、
I think communication is also important,
コミュニケーションも大事だと思うんで、
Communication, uh,
コミュニケーションって、 あの、
I may not have learned it at university, but
大学で習ってないかもしれないですけど、
There are also non-verbal things.
非言語的なやつもあるんですよ
Ah, there it is.
ああ、あります
I'm also trying to communicate,
ちょっと僕もコミュニケーションを図るんで、
For a moment, I was asked to think that I was a senior from the university.
ちょっと 大学のね、 さっきの先輩だと思ってもらって、
We're going to make some progress, so I think you'll be able to go to this area.
ちょっと進めていくんで、 この辺とか行かれると思うんですよ
Oh, your breasts are so soft.
あ、柔らかいですね、おっぱい
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This is probably good communication.
これ多分、コミュニケーションいいですよ
nonverbal communication.
非言語的なコミュニケーション
Is this okay?
ちょっといいですか?
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいです
Is it okay with my hair?
髪でも平気かな?
Hair is fine too.
髪でも大丈夫
Your hair is smooth.
髪サラサラっすね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's really amazing.
本当にすごいっすね
Are you taking care of yourself?
ケアとかしてるの?
I take care of myself, especially my hair and skin.
ケアしてます、髪と肌は特に
It's a woman.
女性ですね
Can I take it home?
持って帰ってもいいですか?
To commemorate Kyoto.
京都記念に
After getting permission from my boyfriend.
彼氏に許可取ってからに
It's piping hot.
熱々っすね
Sorry, I don't think you have permission.
すみません、許可おりないと思う
What about your neck?
首とかどう?
Feeling tickled?
くすぐった気持ち?
Do you feel it much?
あんまり感じる?
My hands are fine.
手は大丈夫です
Oh, you mean breathing?
あ、息とかってこと?
Did you get licked?
舐められたりとか?
Being licked is really ticklish,
舐められたりとかは、 すごい くすぐったくって、
I laugh at how weak it is.
弱くって笑っちゃうんですよ
It's cute.
可愛いっすね
lol Your face is cute.
笑 顔可愛いっすね
I'll push it down a bit.
ちょっと押し倒しますね
I haven't asked for your boyfriend's permission, but please excuse me for a moment.
彼氏許可取ってないですけど、 ちょっと失礼しますね
Your boobs are really soft.
本当に柔らかいね、おっぱい
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
Don't you hate touching your breasts?
おっぱい触れるの嫌いじゃない?
I don't hate it.
嫌いではないです
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしいです
ちょっと恥ずかしいんだ
I'm embarrassed too.
僕も恥ずかしいです
Is it the person touching it?
触ってる本人なの?
This is what it's like now.
こんなになってるんで、今
It's really soft.
本当に柔らかいですね
Gray suits you.
グレーが似合いますね
A gray knit.
グレーのニットが
thank you.
ありがとうございます
That's amazing.
すごいっすね
Like the cleavage.
谷間とかも
beautiful.
綺麗
Her legs are amazing too.
足もすごいっすね
Seriously.
マジで
That's right.
そうなんですよ
It's quite long.
結構長くて
When I say it's quite long, it's quite long.
結構長いって、相当長いっすよ
Is it an ancestor of dinosaurs?
先祖恐竜かな?
A little bit of legs too.
ちょっと足もね
Look at the comparison.
対 比見てよ、これ
Isn't it different at all?
全然違くない?
I've compared women and men.
女性と男性で比べちゃったり
You're so kind.
優しいっすね
It feels like sand in between.
間に砂まさきみたいな感じですよ
It's somewhere between black and white.
黒白で言った中間くらいですよね
that's right.
そうです
It's really smooth, really.
すべすべっすね、マジで
This tickles me.
これくすぐったいからね
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
Can I do this for a moment?
ちょっとやっていいですか?
It's ticklish.
くすぐったいです
Is it okay if I do this much?
これくらいやったら平気?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Your feet are really beautiful.
足本当綺麗っすね
Then, I have a request for you, please use my beautiful feet.
そしたらちょっと 僕のお願いなんですけど 綺麗な足で 僕の
Hey, do you have three legs?
ね、 その 足って3つあるんですか?
Did you know he's a man?
男って知ってました?
Is that so?
そうなんですか?
It's here, but I want you to touch it with your foot.
ここにあるんですけど ちょっとこれを足で 触ってほしいんです
But a little with both feet
けど 両足でちょっと
That's right, even while looking at me,
そうそう、 こっちこそ こっち見ながらさ え、
It's delicious.
うまいっすね
Did you do it?
やってました?
There's nothing I can do.
やっとることないです
Your legs are so beautiful.
足すごい 綺麗っすね
Let's do some magic with this.
これでちょっと魔法かけてください
Is it like this?
こんな感じですか?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいいっすね
That's nice.
いいですね
What's going on?
ちょっとどうなってます?
This giant's feet.
この大さんの足
It's getting hard.
硬くなってます
What do you think?
どうですか?
How hard is it?
硬さは?
About 10.
10くらい
It's like hard, between normal and hard.
硬めみたいな 普通から硬めの間で もうちょっといったらバリ方
in.
で
Is it true?
本当 っすか
So, would you like me to do something for you too?
じゃあ僕もバリ方にするために ちょっと いいですか?
got it.
わかりました
I knead it too.
僕もこねるんでね
got it.
わかりました
That's nice.
いいですね
beautiful.
綺麗
Your feet are really beautiful.
足本当に すごい 綺麗っすね
That's good.
いい ですね
Bali's style is quite good.
バリ方の 結構ノリいいですね
It's surprisingly upbeat.
意 外 にノリいいですね
Is it okay if I go next door?
隣に行っても平気ですか?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
cute.
か わいい
You can see it here.
こっちで 見えますもんね
I understand that you want to go to bed.
ベッド行きたい気持ちは分かります
Would it be okay if there was something like Fees?
フィースとかもあったら平気?
The comparison is amazing.
対比がすごいっすね
Your face is so small.
顔ちっちゃいね
is that so?
そうですか?
That's nice.
いいですね
Can I request the overseas version of the communication as well?
海外版のコミュニケーションも お願いしていいですか?
It feels like it's popping between your lips.
唇と唇で パッって感じ
May I?
いいですか?
It's cute.
かわいいですね
Soft lips.
唇柔らか
Can I try again?
もう一回いいですか?
It has a French feel and an overseas style.
フレンチな感じで 海外風の
Is it okay to take a long time?
長目もいいですか?
It's extremely soft.
めちゃくちゃ柔らかいですね
lips.
唇
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
Then me too
じゃあ 僕も
Check your belongings.
持 ち物チェック
Are you waiting inside?
中待ってないか?
I'm not waiting.
待ってないです
How many cups?
何カップだろう?
Can I guess?
当てていいですか?
Try to guess.
当ててみてください
Once when hitting.
当てるときに一回
Is it about D?
Dくらいですか?
It's D.
Dですね
It looks big.
大きく見えるね
It smells good.
いい匂いしますね
It's extremely soft.
めちゃくちゃ柔らかいです
That's amazing.
すごいですね
I have a request to make.
お願いがありまして
Isn't it a great style?
すごいスタイルいいじゃないですか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Is it okay if I see you in your underwear?
下着姿を見せてもらってもいいですかね?
Would you like to take this off too?
こっちも脱ぎますか?
please.
お願いします
Shall I take my clothes off here?
ここで脱ぎますか?
here.
ここ で
It's bright and embarrassing though.
明るくて恥ずかしいんですけど
So let's keep it dark.
じゃあ暗くしておきますね
Just a little dark.
ちょっとだけ暗く
It's a little out of order, so please leave it as is.
ちょっと故障なので そのままお願いします
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
It really has great style.
めちゃくちゃ本当スタイルいいですね
Can I get a peace?
ピースとかもらってもいい?
cute.
かわいい
It's so cute.
めちゃくちゃかわいいですね
Seriously.
マジで
Men often compliment certain parts of me.
結構男の人には どこのパーツを 褒められたりすることが多い
kana?
かな?
Her breasts, butt, and everything else is quite beautiful.
結 構 胸とかお尻とか 全部きれいですもんね
Can I get a double peace?
ダブルピースとかもらってもいい?
Wow, great style, I like it.
うわー、すげー スタイルいいね、
Seriously.
マジで
beautiful.
きれい
I like the style.
スタイルいいな
odor?
臭い?
odor.
臭い
Smell.
臭 い
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
Try sitting under the sofa.
ソファーの下に座ってみて
Can I see your face?
顔見れる?
Sit a little deeper.
もう少し浅めに座って
Can I have you take off your pants too?
パンツも 脱いでもらってもいいかな?
It's beautiful, body.
きれいだね、体
It remained broken.
割れたままになりましたね
Sit a little deeper.
ちょっと浅めに座って
mango
マンゴ
- Spread it out and show me.
ー 広げて見せてみて
That's amazing.
すごいね
It's pretty easy to get to.
結構行きやすいんだね
It's a bit easy to get to.
ちょっと行きやすい
I went to Mango, take a look.
行ったマンゴーさ、 ちょっと見てみて
Yo.
よ
Are you embarrassed?
恥 ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Spread between the legs.
足刺しの間広げて
You can shake it.
振ってやらしていいよ
Now, try getting to the bottom 4th one.
じゃあ最下4つ目になってみて
I guess it's just a butt.
お尻つきやしかな
Try bending down.
腰そんでみて
Waist.
腰
Spread between the legs.
足刺しの間広げて
Get on your knees and shake it
腰くって振ってみ
hand.
て
Look at this side.
こ っち側見てみて
Look at the left side.
左の方見てみて
Part your hair.
髪かけ分けて
Around here my head.
頭この辺
What kind of doll do you like?
どういう人形が好きとかある?
hardness or thickness.
硬さとか太さとか
I like hard ones.
硬い方が好き
I like the sun.
太陽が好きなんだ
How many points is this?
これ何点くらいですか?
So, is it okay to have 120 points?
じゃあ120点ってことでいいですか?
120 points.
120点
So can I have a look?
じゃあ見てもらっていいですか?
I like the way it's stretched.
その張り方がいいよ
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
Does it feel better this way?
こっちの方が気持ちいいかな?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとだけ
ちょっと だけ
Please stretch your knees.
膝伸ばしてください
Stretch your knees.
膝伸ばして
How did you compare to your boyfriend?
彼氏と比べてどうだった?
Awkward?
気まずい?
It feels so good.
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいいね
It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
Your smile is really nice.
笑顔がやっぱり素敵ですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
nice lips
唇が素敵
is that so?
そうですか?
A slightly unreasonable request.
ちょっと無茶のお願い
This may seem unreasonable, but you can ask for a kissing face.
無茶ぶりするんですけど、 キス顔とかってお願いしてもいい
Is it?
ですか?
What does a kissing face look like?
キ ス顔ってどんな感じですか?
That's what I'm wearing, though.
ちょっと僕被ってるのあれですけど、
If you can do it like that.
って感じでやってもらえると
That's good.
いいっすね
Can I try again?
もう一回いいですか?
Are you glad you did it now?
今のでよかった?
It's fine for now.
今のでいいです
A little longer.
もうちょっと長めに
It's cute.
可愛いですね
I'll give you some pocket money.
ちょっとお小遣いあげちゃいます
I'm happy.
嬉しいです
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Hey, it's that again.
ちょっとね、またあれですね
You came.
来てくれましたね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Should the reason be the same?
理由とかは同じでいいかな?
Ah, the same is fine.
ああ、同じでいい
It's just not enough.
ちょっと足りなくて
After all, it might be my first pocket money,
やっぱね、ちょっと初めての お小遣いかもしれないから、
I might have spent some money.
ちょっと お金使っちゃったかもね
Then you can already see it, right?
そしたらちょっと もう見えてますよね、
Nearby.
近くに
Masaki Sudama.
すだまさき
I'm a little sorry, but for the sake of keeping watch from now on,
ちょっと申し訳ないですけど、 今 後の見張りの都合上ね、
I'm letting you cover some people, but
含めの方を被らせていただいてますけど、
Today I've put together a nice vintage look,
今日 もいい感じの ヴィンテージ具合で まとめてきてるんで、
Hey, it's the best,
ちょっと一番ね、
I don't mind if you take a look at the vintage progress once.
ヴ ィンテージ進行の方を一回ちょっと 見てもらっても平気
Is it?
ですか?
What should I do?
どう すればいいですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Already?
もうすでに?
It's early.
早いですね
Does it feel good?
いい感じですか?
Hey, it's not me today.
ちょっと今日はね、 僕じゃないんですよ
It's not me.
僕じゃないんです
Did you laugh?
笑ってくれました?
Hey, it was that, not me.
ちょっとね、 あれだったんで、 僕じゃないんで、
I feel better towards you, Masaki.
まさき君の方に いい感じになっちゃうんですけど、
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
I miss you so much.
寂しいですね
No, Masaki Suuma is better.
いや、すだまさきの方がいいです
No, no, just ask him to escort you.
いやいや、ちょっと彼に エスコートしてもらってください
It's cute.
可愛いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
This is often said.
よく言われます
Are your boobs big?
おっぱい大きいですか?
Do you think it's bigger?
大きい方だと思いますか?
I think it's big.
大きいと思います
It was really tense.
すごく張ってて
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I want to touch it and can't resist.
触りたくて、 我慢できないです
Well then, fine.
じゃあ、いいですよ
Well then, let me touch you a lot.
じゃあ、いっぱい触らせてもらいます
Well, just once.
じゃあ、ちょっと一回
Is that okay too?
それも、いいですか?
That's also quite expensive.
それも、結構高いんですよ
Hey, what about the little guy?
ちょっと、小さい男の人は?
I don't mind though.
気しないですけど
Don't you care?
気にしない?
It's so kind.
優しいですね
Do you care about the size of your penis?
ちんこの大きさとか、 気 にしますか?
I don't care.
気にしないですね
Well then, I won't tell you to shut up.
じゃあ、黙っておけって話ししませんね
I like the smaller one though.
小さい方が好きですけど
My pelvis is thin, so if it's big it hurts.
骨盤が細いんで、 大きいと痛い
Which one?
ど っちかって
What is the size?
大きさは?
Just right, Honda full.
ちょうどいい、ホンダフル
Is it just right?
ちょうどいい?
Just right, Honda.
ちょうどいい、ホンダ
The topic is different.
ネタが違う
Different generations.
世代が違う
A generation.
世代がね
No one will notice anymore.
もうちょっと、誰も気づかない
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Me too.
僕も
sorry.
す みません
It's humorous.
ユーモアですね
My car was abandoned.
車が捨てられたんで
Mr. Honda.
ホンダさん
Can I have you do it just fine?
ちょうどよくやってもらっていいですか?
It works just fine.
ちょうどよくしますね
Just fine.
ちょ うどよく
Piece the other way.
反対にピースして
That's amazing.
すごいやっぱ
Because my lips are hot.
唇が熱いから
Your lips are amazing, aren't they?
唇がすごいでしょ?
Maybe people don't say that.
そんなこと言わない人多分
That's a great style.
すごいスタイルだね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
That's polite.
丁寧だね
You have a nice butt.
いいお尻してるね
What is a pelvis?
骨盤が何だっけ?
Your pelvis is small.
骨盤がちっちゃいね
The pelvis is narrow.
骨盤が狭い
It's small.
狭いんだ
Is that so?
そう なの?
It's so plump.
すごいプリッとしてる
I'll put this on.
これ被りつけちゃう
Looks like a peach.
桃みたい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Show me your face.
お顔よく見せて
Show me your armpits.
お脇見せて
Side.
お脇
odor?
臭い?
Does it smell a bit?
ちょっと臭いか
You're so soft.
すっごい柔らかいな、お前
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
show me.
見せて
Just listen.
ちょっと耳で
It was so big that I couldn't stand it.
広くてちょっと我慢できなかった
Me.
僕が
Mine was better.
僕の方がよかったですよね
Do you want me to do just the double key?
ダブルキースだけもやってほしい?